Guide to the Joseph Veverka papers, 1942-2013,
Veverka, Joseph papers,
- Series IV. Mission Files
  - Decedal Survey
    - Decadal Primitive Bodies Panel, 2009-09-2009-10 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Decadal Survey September 9-11, 2009, 2009-09 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Decadal Survey New Frontiers, 2008-2011 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - The Space Studies Board 1959-2000, Undated; DVD-3338 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Planetary Science Decadal Survey 2009-2011 Resources Disk 2 v.1, 2009-2011; DVD-3339 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Planetary Science Decadal Survey 2009-2011 Resources Disk 2 v.2, 2009-2011; DVD-3340 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Decadal Survey: Primitive Bodies Notes, Undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Muses-C
    - Muses-C Beth, 1999-05-1999-07 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Muses-C, 1996-10-1997-05 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Solar System Exploration Survey (SSES)
    - NRC, SSES, "New Frontiers", 2002-07 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Solar System Exploration Survey (SSES) Committee August, 2001-04-2001-09 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Solar System Exploration Survey (SSES) Committee October, 2001-01-2001-10 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - SSES, 2001-10-2001-11 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Solar System Exploration, 1998-2007 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Rosetta
    - Rosetta 1997, 1991-1997 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      Contains 2 proposals
    - Deep Rosetta, 2006-03-2008-06 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Committee on Planetary and Lunar Exploration (COMPLEX)
    - Committee on Planetary and Lunar Exploration (COMPLEX) January Boulder, 2007-01 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - COMPLEX July Woods Hole, 2007-06-2007-07 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - COMPLEX, 2007-07-23-2007-07-25; CD-5017 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - The Scientific Context for Exploration of the Moon, Undated; CD-5018 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - An Astrobiology Strategy for the Exploration of Mars, Undated; CD-5019 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - COMPLEX August Washington DC, 2007-06-2007-08 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - COMPLEX April Washington DC, 2007-03-2007-04 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - COMPLEX 4/07, 2007-04; CD-5022 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - COMPLEX Summary of Activities and Perspective on FY 2008 Prospects, 2007-03-06; CD-5023 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - COMPLEX March Washington DC, 2007-03 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - COMPLEX December 2006, 2006-07-2006-12 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - COMPLEX Dec' 2006, 2006-12; CD-5024 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - COMPLEX June Washington DC, 2006-03-2006-06 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - COMPLEX Meeting Presentations Washington, DC, 2008-03-19-2008-03-21; CD-5036 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Space Studies Board (SSB)
    - Space Studies Board (SSB) Woods Hole August, 2006-08 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - SSB 50th Birthday, 2007-08 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Space Studies Board Reports: The Complete Set (2007 Edition), 2007; CD-5020 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - SSB Board Meeting, 2007-03 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - SSB, 2006-09-2007-03 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - SSB November 2006, 2006-09-2006-11 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - SSB General, 2006-01-2006-08 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - SSB Annual Report 2009, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - SSB An Enabling Foundation for NASA's Earth and Space Science Missions, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - SSB Opening New Frontiers in Space: An Evaluation of the New Frontiers Announcement of Opportunity, Undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - SSB Approaches to Future Cooperation and Competition in a Globalizing World, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - SSB Grading NASA's Solar System Exploration Program, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - SSB Choices for the Next New Frontiers Announcement of Opportunity, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - SSB The Scientific Context for Exploration of the Moon, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - SSB Grading NASA's Solar System Exploration Program, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - SSB United States Civil Space Policy, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - SSB Science Opportunities Enabled by NASA's Constellation System, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - SSB 156th Meeting, 2008-06-25 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - SSB CD's, Undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Earth Science and Applications from Space, Undated; CD-5034 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - The Space Studies Board 1958-2008, Undated; CD-5035 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Voyager
    - Voyager at Neptune Poster, Undated (Box mapcase, Folder 1)
- Series V. Course Materials
  - Astronomy 102/104 Our Solar System 1991, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Bound books of notes
  - Astronomy 102/104 Our Solar System 1992, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Astronomy 102/104 Our Solar System 1993, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Astronomy 102/104 Our Solar System 1994, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Astronomy 102/104 Our Solar System 1995, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Astronomy 102/104 Our Solar System 1997, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Astronomy 102/104 Our Solar System 1998, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Astronomy 102/104 Our Solar System 1999, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Astronomy 102/104 Our Solar System 2000, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ASTRO 102/104 2016 Houck, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Our Solar System Exams, 1983-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
    Binder of exams
  - Our Solar System 2000, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 14-16)
    Binder of notes
  - ASTRO 102/104 1992 Slides Book 1, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 17-19)
    Binders of slides
  - ASTRO 102/104 1992 Slides Book 2 Folder 1, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - ASTRO 102/104 1992 Slides Book 2 Folders 2-3, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - ASTRO 102/104 1992 Slides Book 3, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
  - ASTRO 102/104 1992 Slides Book 4, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6-8)
  - ASTRO 671, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
  - ASTRO 671, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ASTRO 671, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - ASTRO 671 Halley's Comet, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - ASTRO 202, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - ASTRO 434 Lecture 5-8, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - ASTRO 331, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - ASTRO 2233, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - ASTRO 202 Correspondence, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - ASTRO 431 1986 lectures, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 2202 Spring 2013, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Slides
  - Class Schedule Deparment of Astronomy, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - ASTRO 2202 Spring 2011, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - ASTRO 2233 Assignmen #1 Fall 2010, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - ASTRO 2202 Spring 2011, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Lecture Slides (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Printed out powerpoint presentations
  - ASTRO 1102/1104 Notes/Planning, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - ASTRO 2233 Fall 2010, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Meteor Articles, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - ASTRO 2202 Unit #4, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - ASTRO 2202, 2000-2012 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - ASTRO 2202 Spring 2012, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - ASTRO 2202, 2009-2011 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - ASTRO 2202 Spring 2011, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - ASTRO 2202, 2011-2012 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - ASTRO 2202, 2012-2013 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - ASTRO 2202, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - ASTRO 2212 Spring 2011, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - What are Comets? Lecture, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - ASTRO 3301 Fall 2011, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - ASTRO 2202 Lecture 25, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - ASTRO 2202/202, 2005-2010 (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
  - ASTRO 1102, 2008-2010 (Box 3, Folder 28-29)
  - ASTRO 2202 Unit 1, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - ASTRO 3301, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - ASTRO 3301, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - ASTRO 2202 Spring 2012, 2012-2013 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - ASTRO 2202 Spring 2013 New Images, 2013; DVD-2814 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - ASTRO 2233, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - ASTRO 2202, 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - ASTRO 2202/202, 2007-2013 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - ASTRO 2233 Fall 2010, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ASTRO 2022 Surveys, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - ASTRO 6570, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - ASTRO 2233 Lecture 14, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - ASTRO 2233 Lecture 4, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - ASTRO 2233, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Lectures/notes ASTRO 2233 and 7671, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Oort Cloud Articles and Lectures, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Lectures on Planets and Comets, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ASTRO 2202 Unit 4, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Gierasch 6575, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Class handouts and handwritten notes
  - Lectures and Articles on Stars and Exoplanets, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - ASTRO 2202/202 Assignments, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - ASTRO 2202, 2011-2012 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - ASTRO 2202 Spring 2011, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - ASTRO 2202 Lecture: Killer Asteroids and Comets, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - ASTRO 2202 Assignment #1, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Lectures and Articles on Comets, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Notes, Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    handwritten notes
  - Enceladus and Saturn, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - ASTRO 332, 1990-2002 (Box 4, Folder 22-23)
    Binders of notes
  - Geology 113, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - ASTRO 671, Undated (Box 4, Folder 25-26)
    Articles and handwritten notes
  - Talk: Comet Excitement Coming Soon!, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Hilo-Joe, 2005-07-24-2005-07-30 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Notes, Pictures, typed documents regarding Hilo workshop
  - ASTRO 2202 Assignments, 2009-2012 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - ASTRO 2202 Habitable planets, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Lectures and Articals on exoplanets, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Lectures on exoplanets and asteroids, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Astro 102/104 spring 1999 slides, Undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
    sheets of slides
  - Galileo Talk Slides, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - ASTRO 2202, String 2011 Questionnaire, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - ASTRO 7671, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Slide Binder 1, Undated (Box 10, Folder 53-55)
  - Slide Binder 2, Undated (Box 10, Folder 56-57)
    contains slides and black and white negatives
  - Slide Binder 3 Folder 1 of 3, Undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Slide Binder 3 Folder 2 and 3 of 3, Undated (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - Slide Binder 4, Undated (Box 11, Folder 3-5)
  - Loose Slides, Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Loose Slides, Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Spacecraft Exploraton of asteroids and Comets, Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Sheets of slides
  - Images, Undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Includes slides and photographs
  - Stars - Notes, Undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Astrology History Notes, Undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Astronomy articles and ASTRO 575 Notes, 1942-1987 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Astro 202 lecture 24 spr. 2005, 2005; CD-5033 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Series VI. Correspondence
  - Rahe, 1991-1997 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Ann Harch, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1982-2012 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Quaide Ltr. Re Role of Pi's JV Response 5/91, 1991-05 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Stephen H. Weiss Presidential Fellows, other correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, articles and images on comets, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    includes a photograph
  - Funding for CONTOUR Correspondence, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, 1995-2004 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Veverka Biography/professional career materials, 1981-2001 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Comet Blurbs-85, 1885-1989 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, 1989-2010 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Card sent to J. Veverka, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Series VII. Veverka Articles and Awards
  - Aviation Week Laureate, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - NASA Group Achievement Award, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Committee work and co-written articles, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    Restricted
  - Veverka co-written article on Trojan Asteroids, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Veverka co-written article on Oberon, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Veverka Report to the National Science Foundation, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Veverka Co-written paper on the Satellites of Jupiter, Undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Veverka article on Asteroids, Undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Veverka Co-written book on Cassini Imaging Science, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Veverka Co-written article on Uranus' Satellites, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Veverka EPOXI Project Team Group Achievement Award, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - The Thermal Evolution of Small Bodies, Joseph Veverka, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Series VIII. Personal Records
  - Thank You Letters for Class Talk, Undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Photos of Veverka, Undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
    Includes Negatives
  - Planning Calender and Letter, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper Mentions, 1997-2005 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Letter to Veverka, Undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Series IX. Grants and Contracts
  - NNX07AAGD4G Investigating…433 Eros, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Grant NAG5-10434, 2001-2005 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Grant NNG06GH27, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Grant Z667704: Deep Impact Project, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - NAG5-11592 Progress Report, 2004-01-01-2006-03-31 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Lee, Pascal, Grant NAG5-11514, Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Grant NAG5-11514 Final Report, 2002-2005 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - NAG5-11514-PGG 2nd Year Annual Report, 2003-11-02 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Grant NAG5-11514 PGG, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - PGG(Planetary Geology and Geophysics) Reviews 2002 Veverka, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Ms. Reviewed for PGG-Veverka, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Veverka, J., PGG, May 2002, Physical Studies of Planetary…, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Regolith processes on Eros from High Resolution Images, NDAP, 2002, Veverka, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Physical Studies of Planetary and Satellite Surfaces, JV, 2001 New Prop., NAG5-3626, 2001-11-2004-04 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Simonelli, PGG, May 2000, Photometric Functions and "Moonshine", 2000 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    Calculations for Upcoming Outer Solar System Missions
  - Physical studies of Planetary and Satellite Surfaces, JV, NAGS-3626, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    includes final report for period ending 2001-10-31
  - Veverka, PGG May 2000 (progress rpt.), Physical Studies of Planetary and Satellite Surfaces, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Veverka, PGG progress rpt. Drafts, Physical Studies of planetary and Satellite Surfaces, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Renewal Proposal: Physical Studies of Planetary and Satellite Surfaces JV, 1999-05 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - NEW PROPOSAL: MUSES-C Mission: Rover Panoramic Near-Imaging Camera Team Leader Proposal, 1998-11 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - New Proposal: Physical Studies of Planetary and Sat. Surfaces, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Physical Studies…" JV 6/97 Progress Proposal Rept., 1997 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Renewal Proposal: Physical Studies of Pl. and Sat. Surfaces NAGW-2186, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - SBSWG Proposal, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Planetary Geology Renewal Proposal-5/95, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Renewal Proposal-NAGW-3591-12/94-Verbiscer, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Revised Proposal _SBSWG - 12/94, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - NEAR Proposal--JV--7/94, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Planetary Geology Renewal Proposal - 4/94, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Final technical report - JPL 959860 (U25-8512) [MASTER], 1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Contract No. 959860 MASTER Mission, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Specification for Technical Documentation Prepared by JPL Contractors, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - MASTER: JPL Proposal, 1994-01-03-1994-04-14 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. 959860, 1994-04-1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - New Proposal CONTOUR, 1993-08-01-1994-09-01 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - New Proposal: "Coordinated Study…" J. Hillier, 1993-07 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Second Year Proposal_NAGW-3837 (JH), 1994-12 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Progress Report-NAGW 3837-JV (Formerly JH grant), 1995-01 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Progress Report: Coordinated Study of Atm. and Surf. Changes on Mars NAGW-3837, 1995-10 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Progress Report: Coordinated Study of Atm. and Surf. Changes on Mars NAGW-3837, 1996-05 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Planetary Geology Renewal Proposal, 1993-03 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - New Proposal: "Asteroid Studies and Collaborative Work", 1993-01 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Hillier/Verbiscer, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Progress Report-'Asteroid Studies', 1993-12 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Small Bodies SWG-Proposal-JV, 1992-11-1995-11 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Suppl. Request - J. Hiller, 1992-05 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Planetary Geology Renewal - Supplement(Computer), 1992-03 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Renewal Proposal - Planetary Surfaces, 1992-03 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Renewal Proposal: Physical Studies of Planetary… (U25-8348), 1991-04 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Final Technical Report, NGT-50482 (A. Verbiscer), 1992 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Contract No. 959068, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Discovery Program Grant Proposal, 1990-11 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Palomar Project - Proposal, 1990-10 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Spacecraft Exploration of Asteroids: The 1988 Perspective JV, YL, RF, MF, Undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Renewal: Spectral Reflectance (U25-8450) NSG-7606, 1990-04 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Phys. Studies of Planetary and Satellite (Renewal) U25-8367, 1990-03 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Uranus Data Analysis Program (UDAP), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - UDAP Proposal-JV, 1988-10-1989-09 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Renewal Proposal: Physical Studies of Planetary and Satellite Surfaces, 1989-03 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Renewal Prop: U25-8367 (NSG-7156), 1998-10-01-1989-09-30 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - U25-8450 "Spectral Reflectance" NSG7606, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Final Technical Report - NAGW-2451 "Discovery" J. Veverka, 1992-02 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Participation in the Voyager Imaging Science Team Contract #956772, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Arizona State Contract 860668-1, U25-8524, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - "Spectral Reflection…" Renewal Proposals, 1983-1986 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Comet Rendezvous Asteroid Flyby (CRAF) Proposal - JV 85, 1979`-1987 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - CRAF Proposal - 11/85 - JV, 1985-11 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - JPL 956772 Extension of Contract, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - U25-8521 VPL957692 Budget Estimate, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Budgets - Voyager U25-8515 JPL956772, 1986-10-01-1987-09-30 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Neptune + Uranus Data Anal Budget, 1986-10-01-1987-90-30 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Budget - U25-8515 - Uranus Encounter, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Final Technical Report - NAGW-193 JV, 1985-05 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - HIIPS Proposal, 1985-01 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Galileo Budget, 1990-1997 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - HIIPS (TSH) Proposal, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Contract No. 958504, 1994-06-20 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Galileo Budget JV-955051, 1986-07-01-1987-12-31 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Galileo HIIPS Amendment, 1986-07-1987-06 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Galileo Budget, 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Participation in the Galileo Orbiter Imaging Science Team, 1981-1994 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Effects of Photometric Geometry on Spectral Reflectance Measurements U25-8450 (renewal) JV, JC, 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Helfenstein, NDAP, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Helfenstein, P., PGG, Sudy of the Effects of Photometric Geometry, 2002-05 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Study of the Effects of Photometric Geom. Phelfenstein, PGG NEW prop., 2001 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Helfenstein, PGG, Study of Optical Spectropolarimetry of Planetary Surfaces in Relation to Geological Characteristics of Regolith, 2000-05 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Helfenstein, PGG, (Progress Rpt.), Study of the effects of the Photometric Geometry on Spectral Reflectance Measurements, 2000-05 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - 2nd Year: Spectral Reflectance PH, 1999-05 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Progress Rept: Digictal Mapping of Jovian Cloud Motions U25-8308 (NAG5-8010), 1999-10 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - NEW PROPOSAL: Digital Mapping of Jovian Cloud Motions PH, 1998-06 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - New Proposal: Spectral Reflectance PH, 1998-05 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Helfenstein, PGG, Progress Rept. Spectral Reflectance, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - NAGW-2084 - Spec. Refl. Measurements FINAL REPORT, 1998-03-24 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Renewal Proposal: Spec. Refl. PH, 1997-06 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Helfenstein - Spec. Refl. Pro., 1997-06 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Renewal Proposal: Spectral Refl. NAGW-2084 (PH), 1996-04 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Renewal Proposal: "Spectral Reflectance" U25-8470 PH, 1995-05 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Renewal Proposal - Spectral Refl., 1993-04 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Renewal Proposal - Spectral Refl., 1994-04 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - RENEWAL PROPOSAL: Spectral Reflectance (U25-8470), 1992-03 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - RENEWAL PROPOSAL: Spectral Reflectance (U25-8470), 1991-04 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - RENEWAL PROPOSAL: "Spectral Reflectance Proposal", 1989-03 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Review 09-PGG09-0027 Spectral Invest. of Gaspra, Ida, Dactyl, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Review 09-PGG09-0021 Accurate Det. Of Asteroid Surface Mineralogy, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Investigating Detailed Seismic Effects of Large Impacts on the Surface morphology of asteroid 433 Eros Jim Richardson - PI, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Topography, Structure and Stratigraphy of Tempel-1 Peter Thomas - PI, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Pheobe and Hyperion: Surface Effects of Large Impacts Jim Richardson - PI, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - PGG Proposal - Jim Richardson, 2005-05-06 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Proposal "Regolith Generation and Redistribution of 433 Eros Peter Thomas, Collaborator, 2005-04 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - "New Analysis of Voyager IRIS Spectra from Jupiter and Saturn" Proposal Rejection, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - H-ALFA: A Survey of the Star Formation..Giovanelli and Haynes, 2004-10 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - MARDI - Peter Thomas, Co-I, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - NASA - Camera Handlens And Mictroscope Probe (CHAMP), Pascal Lee/Joe Veverka, 2004-05-07 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - NASA - Study of the Effects of Photometric Geometry…Paul Helfenstein, 2004-05-07 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - NASA PGG03-0047-0061 Surgaces of Planets: Eolian History on Mars and Other Topics P. Thomas, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Mars Dust Storm and Polar Meteorology Studies using MGS Data, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - NASA New Analysis of Voyager IRIS Spectra Peter Gierasch, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - NASA New Analysis of Voyager IRIS Spectra Peter Gierasch, 2004-04-23 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - NSF 0407020 - Gierasch Modeling Deep Seasonal Variations In Uranus, 2001-2003 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Series X. Audio/Visual Material
  - Unlabeled Negatives, Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Unlabeled Negatives, Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Unlabeled Negatives, Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Unlabeled Negatives, Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Unlabeled Slides, Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Unlabaled Slides, Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Unlabeled Slides, Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Material Accompanying CD-5051, 2004-04-19 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Deep Impact: Excavating Comet Tempel 1, 2006-01; CD-5043 (Box 14)
  - Comet Clipper, 2004-02-13; CD-5044 (Box 14)
    New Frontiers Mission Proposal AO 03-OSS-03
  - Science Case for CCAT, Undated; CD-5045 (Box 14)
  - Near-Earth Asteroid Operations: Astronaut Activities?, 2006-07-06; CD-5046 (Box 14)
    Academie Internationale D'Astronoutique (IAA)
  - Deep Impact, Undated; CD-5047 (Box 14)
  - 4 More Presentations, Undated; CD-5048 (Box 14)
  - Overview of Scientific Results from the Deep Impact Mission, 2006-01-24; CD-5049 (Box 14)
    Michael Belton
  - CCAT Steering Committee Karla Consroe, Undated; CD-5050 (Box 14)
  - Earth and Space Sciences Division Visition Committee External Review, 2004-03-11-2004-03-12; CD-5051 (Box 14)
  - Digital Lunar Orbiter Photographic Atlas, 2000; CD-5052 (Box 14)
    A digital archive of Lunar Orbiter Images
  - Cornell and CONTOUR Comet Challenge, Undated; CD-5053 (Box 14)
    CD Compilation of Images and Video Clips for use in Comet Challenge Outreach Projects
  - "News from Mars" PowerPoint Presentation, Undated; CD-5054 (Box 14)